Hoàng Thành Đạt

RESEARCH AND DEVELOPMENT SPECIALIST

- O363604119
- ■ dathoangcet@gmail.com
- Khang Gia Apartment Complex, Block A, Ward 14, Go Vap District, Ho Chi Minh City

OBJECTIVE

With over a year of experience as an embedded developer, I have worked on developing firmware for devices such as Ambi Climate, HMI Delta control panel, and security key. Additionally, as a Research and Development Specialist, I have a strong knowledge of FIDO and application development using Flutter. Look forward to joining company to make creative and innovative business solutions for its impressive global clients

WORK EXPERIENCE

VinCSS

10/2023 - present

TMA Solutions

5/2023 - 8/2023

VNNEXT Academy

6/2022 - 3/2024

RESEARCH AND DEVELOPMENT SPECIALIST

Develop firmware for security key

Building an application to update firmware for devices using Flutter

EMBEDDED DEVELOPER

Develop firmware EVT and pre - production for Ambi device

Develop firmware production for Delta HMI control panel for AGV

STEM TEACHER / LEADER OF TEACHER TEAM

Design STEM programs and tools

Teach programming to young children

PROJECTS

Ambi Device

5/2023 - 7/2023

Ambi Climate

5 Firware Developer, 2 QA, 1 Dev Ops, 2 Android developer, 1 IOS developer, 1 backend, 1 Al developer

RESPONSIBILITIES

Write drivers for components on Ambi board by esp-idf Prefactor code for pre-production firmware

TECHNOLOGIES

- FreeRTOS
- · Cloud serivces: AWS
- Communication protocols: I2C, SPI, RMT, UART
- · Connectivity: WiFi, BLE
- IoT communication protocols: MQTT, HTTP

Delta HMI control panel for AGV

7/2023 - 8/2023

STI Việt Nam

2 Firmware Developer

RESPONSIBILITIES

Develop production firmware according to customer requirements

TECHNOLOGIES

- FreeRTOS
- · Communication protocols: Modbus RTU
- IoT communication protocols: WebSocket

Security key

10/2023 - 2/2024

VinCSS

2 firmware Developer

RESPONSIBILITIES

Develop production firmware based on the features specified by the company Implementing FIDO2 in the device

Develop read/write data functionality and partition the flash memory

Develop a desktop app to update the firmware of the security key for customers.

TECHNOLOGIES

- Using FIDO2 for the registration and authentication process with the security key on various devices.
- · Connectivity: BLE, NFC, HID
- Using Flutter to build a desktop app (Windows and macOS) for updating firmware to customers over the internet.

EDUCATION

2020 - 2024

COMUPTER ENGINEERING TECHNOLOGY

HO CHI MINH CITY UNIVERSITY OF TECHNOLOGY AND EDUCATION

- GPA: 8.43/10 (3.34/4)
- Deputy Secretary of the class union for three terms
- 2 semesters with scholarships
- Design and build playfields for competing teams.
- Train the competing teams on knowledge related to the competition.
- Technical support throughout the course of the event.

SKILLS

FIRMWARE DEVELOPMENT SKILLS

- Strong in C/C++, python programming for Embedded Software Development
- Knowledge with Java, Flutter for building mobile app and desktop app
- Experience with microcontroller: ESP32, STM32, NRF52840, 8051
- Experience with communication protocols: SPI, I2C, RMT, UART, Modbus RTU
- Experience with connectivity: WIFI, BLE, GSM/GPRS, RF, LoraWan, NFC
- Knowledge with IoT data protocol: MQTT, HTTP/HTTPS, web socket
- Good knowledge and hands-on experience in RTOS
- Knowledge of various types of memory: EEPROM, NVS, RAM, and flash
- Knowledge with cloud services: AWS, Firebase

ACTIVITIES

CERTIFICATIONS

2020 - 2022

HONORS & AWARDS

10/2021 - 9/2022

INNOVATION AND APPLICATION CLUB

Deputy technical department

- Brainstorm ideas and organize engineering contests at Ho Chi Minh University of Technology and Education
- Technical training for new collaborators

17/01/2023

Attested score of 720 on the TOEIC exam

 Top 8 RFSpeed Racing Competitions and Hi-Tech Chirstmas Gift

• Top 16 Animal Robot Season 3